(camera clicks)
(Sheldon:)All you did was offer
(Sheldon:)maternal care and affection,
(Sheldon:)and all you received in return
(Sheldon:)was rude and insensitive
behavior.
(Penny:)Can this wait?
(Sheldon:)I'm afraid it can't.
(Sheldon:)The trip is tomorrow.
(Leonard:)And I have
more apologies to make.
(Penny:)Okay, fine, I accept
your apology, now get out!
(Sheldon:)Wonderful. would you mind
holding up this shirt
while I take a quick...?
Leonard!
(Sheldon:)You brought me my comic books
when I wasn't feeling well.
That-that was
thoughtful.
(Sheldon:)And I was insensitive.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Stuart:)Thank you, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I appreciate that.
(Sheldon:)And I want you to know
that I mean it, you know?
(Sheldon:)This isn't me just wanting to
go on the trip to Las Vegas.
(Stuart:)What trip to Las Vegas?
(Sheldon:)The one everyone's taking
(Sheldon:)this weekend on the party bus.
(Stuart:)Of course, I wasn't invited.